(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Thank you all for joining us today for Baelz Hakos's Birthday Live 2026.
Before we begin, I have a few requests and reminders for everyone.
Feel free to enjoy food and drinks in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone, but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
The official hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D. Please post about us on social media.
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone during the show is more than welcome.
We'd love it if you could share them online to help spread the excitement.
The show will begin shortly, so please stay tuned.
皆様、本日はハコス・ベールズ生誕祭2026にお越しくださいまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you all very much for coming to Baelz Hakos's Birthday Live 2026 today.
開演に先立ちまして、皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
Before the show starts, we have some requests and announcements for you.
テレビやパソコン、スマートフォンの前では飲食は可能ですが、キーボードにこぼさないようにお気をつけください。
Feel free to eat and drink in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone, but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
当配信のハッシュタグは #ReCOLOR3D です。SNSでたくさんポストしてください！
The hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D. Please post a lot on social media!
開演中、カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影は大歓迎です。たくさんポストして盛り上がってくださいますと幸いです。
Taking photos with cameras or smartphones during the show is highly welcomed. We'd appreciate it if you'd post a lot and share the excitement.
それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Now then, please wait a little longer until the show begins.
Thank you all for joining us today for Baelz Hakos's Birthday Live 2026.
Before we begin, I have a few requests and reminders for everyone.
Feel free to enjoy food and drinks in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone, but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
The official hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D. Please post about us on social media.
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone during the show is more than welcome.
We'd love it if you could share them online to help spread the excitement.
The show will begin shortly, so please stay tuned.
皆様、本日はハコス・ベールズ生誕祭2026にお越しくださいまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you all very much for coming to Baelz Hakos's Birthday Live 2026 today.
開演に先立ちまして、皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
Before the show starts, we have some requests and announcements for you.
テレビやパソコン、スマートフォンの前では飲食は可能ですが、キーボードにこぼさないようにお気をつけください。
Feel free to eat and drink in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone, but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
当配信のハッシュタグは #ReCOLOR3D です。SNSでたくさんポストしてください！
The hashtag for this stream is #ReCOLOR3D. Please post a lot on social media!
開演中、カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影は大歓迎です。たくさんポストして盛り上がってくださいますと幸いです。
Taking photos with cameras or smartphones during the show is highly welcomed. We'd appreciate it if you'd post a lot and share the excitement.
それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Now then, please wait a little longer until the show begins.
光の速さで 駆け抜ける衝動は
The impulse that races past at the speed of light
何を犠牲にしても 叶えたい強さの覚悟
is the determination of strength to make it come true, whatever the cost.
(No fear) 一度きりの
(No fear) Only once
(Trust you) この瞬間に
(Trust you) in this moment
賭けてみろ 自分を信じて
Try betting on it, believing in yourself
時には運だって必要と言うのなら
If you say that sometimes even luck is necessary
宿命の旋律も引き寄せてもみせよう
I will show you that I can pull even the melody of fate to myself
走れ 今を まだ終われない
Run! The present is not over yet
辿り着きたい場所があるから
Because there is a place I want to reach
その先へと進め
Advance to what lies beyond!
涙さえも強く胸に抱きしめ
Holding even my tears firmly in my chest
そこから始まるストーリー
The story that begins from there
果てしなく続く Winning the soul
will continue endlessly... winning the soul!
掴め 今を変えたいなら
Grab it! If you want to change the present
描いた夢を未来に掲げ
Raise the dream you drew into the future
恐れないで挑め
And don't be afraid to challenge it!
走れ 今を まだ終われない
Run! The present is not over yet
辿り着きたい場所があるから
Because there is a place I want to reach
その先へと進め
Advance to what lies beyond!
涙さえも強く胸に抱きしめ
Holding even my tears firmly in my chest
そこから始まるストーリー
The story that begins from there
果てしなく続く Winning the soul
will continue endlessly... winning the soul!
Woh woh woh
What's up, everyone!
I am Chaos, the end of ends,
a steel rat trapped in the cage of ice, your best friend Baelz Hakos from Hololive English -Promise-!
我は混沌、終わりの果て、ザ・エンド！
I am Chaos, the end of ends, the end!
氷の牢に封印されし、黒鉄の薔薇！
A black iron rose sealed in a cage of ice!
汝の友、ホロライブのハコス・ベールズです！
Your friend, Baelz Hakos of Hololive!
Witness me!!!
Another year, another Not-Birthday Live!
Thank you so much for coming, everyone!
Did you like the opening act?
The opening show, did ya, did ya?
Thank you so much for coming, everyone!
This year, we have a Not-Birthday Birthday Live again called...
ReCOLOR 3D!
That is also the hashtag, please use it! #ReCOLOR3D
Um, and I know it might be... the theme this year was color, for, for, for many reasons.
There's also a lot of special things that are happening today,
as you may or may not already know.
There's a lot of new things being revealed in this live.
Maybe a new song?
Maybe a new outfit?
I don't know, you're just gonna have to wait and see!
えっと、今年も誕生日じゃない誕生日ライブやりたいと思います。みんな来てくれてありがとうございます！
So, I'm doing another Not-Birthday Birthday Live this year. Thank you all for coming!
えー、今日のライブでね、新しいものいっぱいあると思いますので、
Um, in today's live, there's going to be lots of new things, so...
最後まで、見に、見てくれたら嬉しいです！
...I'd be happy if you watched until the very end!
あー、もう疲れてる、やばい。
Ah, I'm already tired. Oh no!
はい！
Yes!
あの、ハッシュタグも、ぜひぜひ、あの、いっぱいコメントと写真をポストしてください！ありがとうございます。
Please also use the hashtag to post lots of comments and photos! Thank you!
It is my birthday... Not-Birthday,
but I'm just so excited to be able to share this day with all of you.
Once I catch my breath,
we're gonna get this party started, yeah?
じゃあ、最後まで楽しんでください！
So, please enjoy until the very end!
そこ、次の曲にちょっと... I'm gonna go to the other stage for the next song, so I'll see you guys there, all right?
And now, for the next song... I'm gonna go to the other stage, so I'll see you guys there, all right?
I'm gonna, I'm gonna go now.
Um, is that all right? Okay, bye. I'll see you guys there.
Race you!
あれが正解なんて
That's supposed to be the correct answer?
誰の成れの果て？
Whose ruined end is that?
なんだっての悶々々
What's with this agonizing...
答えも欲しいのも一個てこれだけ
There's only one answer I want, and it's just this.
悩んだってしょうがないじゃんね
It's no use worrying about it, right?
あれは夢だったって思うことにしたって
Even if I try to convince myself it was just a dream...
（つらｗ）でも全然思えないんだけど
(Painful, lol) But I can't think of it that way at all.
助けてよフォロワー！抗うだけ
Help me, followers! I'll just keep resisting.
若さに負け next, next, lucky, lucky, lucky
Losing to youth, next, next, lucky, lucky, lucky.
アーリーオ 割り切れなったらさ
Ah-ree-oh, if I could just divide it cleanly...
オーリーオ 楽なのにとか
Oh-ree-oh, it would be so much easier...
あぁ もうヤダ！
Ah, I've had enough of this!
なんという新世界か！
What kind of new world is this!
あなた以外は
Anyone other than you...
あなた以外はいらない ない ない
Anyone other than you, I don't need, need, need!
はらないでよバリア
Don't put up a barrier!
あるはずなの何か
There must be something there...
あったならば happy, jumpin', yeah
If there is, happy, jumpin', yeah!
あなたのその手と
Your hand...
あたしのこの手を
...and my hand.
つないだら もう二度と離さないわ
If we hold hands, I'll never let go again.
あなたのその手が
If your hand...
あたしのこの手を
...grabs my hand...
掴んだら... 以後お見知りおきを！ my love ♡
...well, pleased to make your acquaintance, my love!
これで終わりなんて
That this is the end...
アガれないままなんて
...without even getting hyped up?
どうにかなっちゃえって願って願って
Praying and praying for something to happen.
ねぇ 朝帰りしたりしちゃわん？どう？
Hey, wanna stay out all night? What do you say?
なあ もう我慢できん！ pain, pain
Ah, I can't stand it anymore! Pain, pain.
痛いってば everyday
I'm saying it hurts everyday!
ま ゆーていけるけどな
Well, I mean, I can handle it though.
ブルベ夏なんで関係ないな
I'm a cool summer type, so it doesn't matter.
誰よりもネコ
More of a cat than anyone else.
節操ないも結構
Having no morals is perfectly fine.
あーしはあーしだ
I am who I am.
見といてよready
Keep your eyes on me, ready?
もう今日で終わらせたいなって
I want to end it all today...
リスタートできたらって
...if only I could get a restart.
でも無理よ もう
But it's impossible, already!
what's on your mind?
アーリーオ 割り切れなったらさ
Ah-ree-oh, if I could just divide it cleanly...
オーリーオ 楽なのにとか
Oh-ree-oh, it would be so much easier...
あぁ もうヤダ！
Ah, I've had enough of this!
あぁ！
Aaaah!
なんという新世界か！
What kind of new world is this!
あなた以外は
Anyone other than you...
あなた以外はいらない ない ない
Anyone other than you, I don't need, need, need!
はらないでよバリア
Don't put up a barrier!
あるはずなの何か
There must be something there...
あったならば happy, jumpin', yeah
If there is, happy, jumpin', yeah!
あなたのその手と
Your hand...
あたしのこの手を
...and my hand.
つないだら もう二度と離さないわ
If we hold hands, I'll never let go again.
あなたのその手が
If your hand...
あたしのこの手を
...grabs my hand...
掴んだら... 以後お見知りおきを！ my love ♡
...well, pleased to make your acquaintance, my love!
な な な な
Na-na-na-na...
おぉ おぉ
Oh, oh...
以後お見知りおきを！ my love ♡
Pleased to make your acquaintance, my love!
らりらりらった らりら
Lari lari latta lari la...
[曲名: CR詠ZY]
[Song: CR詠ZY]
Break away, Break away 細胞レベル
Break away, break away, on a cellular level.
あのユニフォーム着こなせてる？
Can you pull off that uniform?
姿 仕草 そこそこでしょ
Your figure and gestures are just so-so, aren't they?
Don't you think? Don't you think?
I'm so lazy 多分トップファイブ
I'm so lazy, probably top five.
そんな並べてるだけの人
Just a person standing in line like that.
Crash, crash, toss away
Don't you think? Don't you think?
In this world この頭には
In this world, in this head of mine...
What a beautiful 散る花びら
What a beautiful scattering of petals.
バラライカのみたいな
Just like a balalaika.
らりらりらった らりら
Lari lari latta lari la.
誰もが偉大
Everyone is great.
C-R-A-Z-Y
一瞬の感情に
In a fleeting emotion...
Ride on, Ride on, Ride on, Ride on
心は ninety-five
My heart is at ninety-five.
狂気のサムライ
A crazy samurai.
血走る生存線でいくライフ
Going through life on a bloodshot lifeline...
Ready to die
HELLO 陽は昇り あなたの空 まっ暗な空
HELLO, the sun is rising, but your sky is pitch black.
荒々しく弾く響き ちぎって
Tearing apart the roughly played echoes.
ほら その場所で 聴こえてくる鼓動の仕掛け
Look, at that place, the mechanism of the beating heart you can hear.
轟くのは己の調べ 誰のものでもない 己の調べ
What roars is my own melody, belonging to no one else, my own melody!
Rat-tat-tat, rat-tat-tat
目の前に広がる世界はブルー
The world spreading before my eyes is blue.
ひとまずさあ MOVE
For now, let's MOVE.
Tick-tack, tick-tack, there's no need 何そんな張り切って偉そうに
Tick-tack, tick-tack, there's no need, why are you so eagerly acting high and mighty?
あぁ 君も愛を 右も左も
Ah, you too, love, left and right...
知りもしないで言わないで Don't you think? Don't you think?
Don't talk without even knowing, don't you think? Don't you think?
にやり 影が笑う
Grinning, the shadow laughs.
世界は異様
The world is bizarre!
C-R-A-Z-Y
繰り返すよう
It seems to repeat...
Ride on, Ride on, Ride on, Ride on
分かってもいない
You don't even understand.
あの子のようと...
Like that girl...
Tell me something for the new...
偉大な 期待の 時代の 舞台
To the stage of a great, expectant era
Go!
Clap back
Losing my mind, shooting my sign
Favorite あなたのその瞬間 Maybe nothing wrong, nothing wrong
Favorite, that moment of yours, maybe nothing wrong, nothing wrong
Ladi-ladi-la-ta, ladi-ladi-la
Hey! 誰も彼も大体
Hey! Everyone is mostly...
Hey! C-R-A-Z-Y
Hey! 一瞬の感情に write on, write on, write on, write on
Hey! Ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on a momentary emotion!
Hey! 心は 95
Hey! The heart is 95
Hey! 狂いだす samurai
Hey! A samurai starting to go crazy
Hey! 血走らせた目で 100, 99 ready, ready to die
Hey! With bloodshot eyes, 100, 99... ready, ready to die!
Ready to die
美々々にしろ注意
Be-be-be careful
あいつの信者は多い
They have many followers
己を知りなさい bitch
Know yourself, bitch
HDで魅えるのに
Even though you can see in HD
私もあなた様みたいになりたい
I want to be like you too
教えて教えて幸せですよね？
Tell me, tell me, you are happy, right?
もしこのまま消えたら愛されるのなら
If I could be loved by disappearing like this
今すぐにでも綺麗に亡くなりたい
I would want to disappear beautifully right now
こんなはずないわよ ダヴィンチ
It shouldn't be like this, Da Vinci
もう少しだけべっぴんに
Make me a little more beautiful
コントラストも入れて頂戴
Please add some contrast
全世界を懲らしめたい
I want to punish the whole world
Look at this, uh
Look at this
Look at this 悲しいかも ayy, ayy, ayy
Look at this, maybe it's sad, ayy, ayy, ayy
もう少し肌に艶を頂戴
Please give my skin a little more gloss
女盛り舐めたらヤイ
Don't mess with a woman in her prime
トイレに女神はおったんかい？
Were you a goddess in the restroom?
おったなら捕まえなさい
If you were, then catch her
ちゃんみな最近まじかわいい
"Chanmina is really cute lately"
私は忘れないあの嵐
I won't forget that storm
あの時私はまだセブンティーン
At that time, I was still seventeen
あの時言ったよな
You said it back then, didn't you?
You can't be beautiful
You can't be famous
醜いブスが歌ってんじゃないよ
Don't sing, you ugly bitch
あの時狂った精神に才能が開花
My talent bloomed in my crazed mind at that time
味わった幸も不幸も一般じゃなかった保存版
The happiness and unhappiness I experienced were not normal
本物を君は知ってるかい？
Do you know what's real?
知識と経験のエロス
Eros of knowledge and experience
まだ使いもんになってるかい？
Are you still being useful?
女は皆正気じゃない保存版
Women are all a bit crazy
Hakos Baelz!
Look at this
Look at this 悲しいかも ayy, ayy, ayy
Look at this, maybe it's sad, ayy, ayy, ayy
もう少し肌に艶を頂戴
Please give my skin a little more gloss
女盛り舐めたらヤイ
Don't mess with a woman in her prime
トイレに女神はおったんかい？
Were you a goddess in the restroom?
おったなら捕まえなさい
If you were, then catch her
Can you hear me mina, are you the beauty?
Say July, you are the mother fucking beauty
予想違い驚きなさい
Unexpected, be surprised
磨いたらダイヤ美しい
If you polish it, it's a diamond, beautiful
前例がないのは怖いかい？
If there's no precedent, are you scared?
磨いたらダイヤ美しい
If you polish it, it's a diamond, beautiful
ならお手本になりなさい
Then become a model
生きなさい今魅せなさい
Live, show it now
怖がったままでどうすんだい？
What are you going to do while being scared?
あなたこそダイヤ美しい
You are the diamond, beautiful
I'm a fucking woman
And I'm fucking beautiful
God, here I am
We're fucking women
And we're fucking beautiful, yeah
Look everyone! I finally have a new outfit!
見て見て見て！新衣装どう？かわいい？
Look, look, look! How is my new outfit? Is it cute?
どう？どう？どう？ Do I look cute? Or...
How is it? Do I look cute? Or...
Is performance Bae... Ahhh!
You wanna have a close-up? There's so many things I wanna show off!
Starting from... let's start from the top, top-down. From the head...
Look at that hair! Look at that fit!
かっこよくない？
Isn't it cool?
I asked for a wolf cut
Um, that's also up half, up half-down, so it's really easy to dance in.
めっちゃ踊りやすくて...
It's super easy to dance in...
かわいいでしょ？ま、かわいい、かっこいいでしょ？
It's cute, right? Well, cute, cool, right?
And then, uh, what else, what else?
Oh, my makeup!
メイクも可愛いっしょ？
My makeup is also cute, right?
Hehehe!
And then I have so many like hand accessories as well!
Look at that! Look how cool that is!
And then we'll do like a quick scan of the...
...T-pose quick scan, quick scan of the body!
Whoa! Whoa!
There's also something very special.
I have an MC tail now.
If you noticed, uh, earlier, normally when I dance, I have my...
...tail just, you know, free. But, you know, this is...
...the MC resting tail. Because the tail also needs resting periods as well, so...
...this is my MC tail. Very cute!
I hope you guys like it! Oh my god!
And this was designed by, of course, the amazing Mika-mama!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
めちゃくちゃ可愛いデザインになりました！
It turned into a super cute design!
ありがとうございます。へへ。
Thank you very much. Hehe.
But that's not all!
I mean, if I get a new outfit, I feel like...
...it's only fair that some other people get new outfits!
こいこい、来て来て来て！
Come, come, come here!
The Bae Dancers also get new outfits!
You get an outfit, you get an outfit, everyone gets an outfit! Look at them!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah? Oh, wow! Oh, so sexy, oh!
So the new dancers have also upgraded outfits!
They have shorts with the boots, and the socks, and the jacket...
Wow, look at that! Amazing!
And then on the back of the jacket, they have my logo.
後ろにロゴもあります！
There's also a logo on the back!
可愛い！
So cute!
Also, I designed... uh, not designed, but I wanted the design...
...to be easy for them to dance in as well, so...
This is the upgraded Bae Dance Team!
どう？可愛い？
How is it? Cute?
アン、ポーズ。
And, pose.
ポーズ。
Pose.
可愛い！イェーイ！
Cute! Yay!
まあ、せっかくなんでね。
Well, since we're here...
Since we all have new outfits, I think it's only fitting that we continue the rest of the live...
...like this, with our new outfits!
じゃ、踊りましょうか！
Well, shall we dance?
We're going to do the next song on the stage over there.
行こう！
Let's go!
おいしょ、おいしょ、おいしょ、おいしょ。
Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho...
Woo!
おいしょ、おいしょ。いや、緊張するな。
Heave-ho, heave-ho. Man, I'm nervous.
はい！じゃ、どうぞ！
All right! Here you go!
正体あらわせ
Reveal your true form!
月の光を飲む 僕の夜が来た
Drinking the moonlight, my night has come.
けたたましく現われる one two
Appearing noisily, one two.
危険を探して knock, knock, knock!!
Searching for danger, knock, knock, knock!
Don't mess it up! Forget it, make a finger
窓を見て you can see my eyes
Look through the window, you can see my eyes.
その瞳に出会ったら
If you meet those eyes,
お前は仲間だ カムカム say it!
you are one of us, come come, say it!
けしやうのものか ましやうのものか
Is it a phantom? Is it a demon?
正体あらわせ ay ta da da da da
Reveal your true form, ay ta da da da da!
変装して love it 僕見て know it らいらいらいらいや
Disguised, love it, look at me, know it, lai-lai-lai-lai-ya.
明かせ love it 存在 know it いないいないばぁ
Reveal it, love it, presence, know it, peek-a-boo.
Don't worry 傷つけないよ ライアイア
Don't worry, I won't hurt you, lai-ai-ar.
I let you このミステリーに あいやいやいやいや-
I let you into this mystery, ai-ya-ya-ya-ya...
See this finger trap!
明日は make it rough 今日は make it fire
Tomorrow, make it rough, today, make it fire.
目を避け ないで make it loud your voice
Don't look away, make your voice loud.
よしよし止せ恐れ
Alright, alright, stop fearing.
お狐様に任せよ！
Leave it to the Queen Fox!
光を騙して作るんだ night
Tricking the light to create a night.
あちこち目覚めて闇が喝采
Awakening here and there, the darkness applauds.
ねぇほらこっちおいで
Hey, come over here.
Yeah! just shout out the spell!
けしやうのものか ましやうのものか
Is it a phantom? Is it a demon?
正体あらわせ ay ta da da da da
Reveal your true form, ay ta da da da da!
未体験 love it 僕 は know it らいらいらいらいや
Unexperienced, love it, I know it, lai-lai-lai-lai-ya.
この世界変える see me 期待して
Changing this world, see me, expect it.
Don't worry 傷つけないよ ライアイア
Don't worry, I won't hurt you, lai-ai-ar.
I let you さあ魑魅魍魎に あいやいやいやいや-
I let you, now, into the demons, ai-ya-ya-ya-ya...
Hey! follow the queen fox
I'm the real master of this night
Hey! follow your queen fox
魅せられて dan dan dan
Fascinated, dan dan dan.
重なり合った世界 僕たちの show window
Our overlapping worlds are like a show window.
見透かすこの眼差し 君に届いてる？
Is this piercing gaze reaching you?
Why don't you know? It's time now
どんな姿でも構わない世界へ
To a world where any appearance doesn't matter!
けしやうのものか ましやうのものか
Is it a phantom? Is it a demon?
正体あらわせ
Reveal your true form!
正体を現せ
Reveal your true form
Heh, pseudo-lover 組み敷いてんの？
Heh, pseudo-lover, are you pinning them down?
Lai, lai, lai, lai, lai
Ah, castle-lover 存在の意？
Ah, castle-lover, is there any meaning to your existence?
Nai, nai, nai, nai, nai
Don't worry 傷つけないよ
Don't worry, I won't hurt you
Lai, ya, ya
I'll let you このミステリーを
I'll let you... into this mystery
Lai, ya, ya, ya, ya
I'll let you 察して耳元に
I'll let you... sense it right in your ear
Lai, ya, ya, ya, ya, ya
Sweet finger trap
Just shout out the spell
Woah...
Yeah, full-on Queen Fox!
Ah... Ah... Ah...
時には噛んだりして 痛みを覚えさせて
Sometimes bite me, and make me remember the pain
溢れる液体で 汚してよ 全部
With your overflowing fluids, stain everything
足の先からずっと 馳せあがるその神経はもう
From the tips of my toes, the nerves that race up
感触に溺れる 身体 心を連れて
My body, drowning in sensation, takes my heart along
指くわえた我慢の中
Sucking on my finger in restraint
欲してんのが理想
What you desire is the ideal
いらない 全てはいらない
I don't need it, I don't need any of it
磨き上げてる邪魔なPRIDE
This annoying pride I've polished up
無意味な世界のルールくらい
Even the meaningless rules of this world
無駄としか言いようがない
There's no word for them but useless
隠しているあなたのSTYLE
Your hidden style
剥き出しにあるがまま DIVE
Exposed just as you are, dive
そこに生まれるのは期待
What is born there is expectation
外れなんかじゃない 頂きのSMILE
It's no miss, it's the smile at the peak
Ah... Ah... Ah...
吐息を合わせた相性 耳に吹きかける感情
Our breaths aligning in compatibility, emotions whispered into my ear
破裂しそうな胸 騒ぎだす細胞
My chest is about to burst, cells starting to stir
脱ぎかけてるシャツ 優しく裂いてよ まず
First, gently tear the shirt I've half-slipped off
構わず get fly もう 収まらないで
Without a care, get fly, don't hold back anymore
自由な世界のど真ん中
Right in the middle of this free world
夢見てるのなら同情
If you're dreaming, you have my pity
いらない 全てはいらない
I don't need it, I don't need any of it
怯えきっている野望のTRY
This frightened attempt at ambition
満足感なんてそこにない
There is no satisfaction to be found there
目に見えるあわれな未来
The pitiful future clearly in sight
思い通りにできるLIFE
A life that can be led exactly as desired
手にできるかはあなた次第
Whether you can grasp it is up to you
隠したりなんかはしない
I won't hide anything
誰よりも誇らしげにできる舞
Dancin' more proudly than anyone else
ほら この世界の中
Look, inside this world
他にはいない
There's no one else
確かなもの
Something certain
自分以外は皆無
Except for myself, there's nothing
Stop, drop, and roll, bite your mind, start the motor, alright.
Don't get cheap, coordinate, fully...
全開で Let's burn, burn, burn!
At full throttle, let's burn, burn, burn!
欲しがってんのはそう 気持ちいいのをもっと
What I want is, yes, even more pleasure
あるがままの思い入れ 魂で DANCE!
With my feelings just as they are, let's dance with our souls!
いらない 全てはいらない
I don't need it, I don't need any of it
磨き上げてる邪魔なPRIDE
This annoying pride I've polished up
無意味な世界のルールくらい
Even the meaningless rules of this world
無駄としか言いようがない
There's no word for them but useless
隠しているあなたのSTYLE
Your hidden style
剥き出しにあるがまま DIVE
Exposed just as you are, dive
そこに生まれるのは期待
What is born there is expectation
外れなんかじゃない 頂きのSMILE
It's no miss, it's the smile at the peak
ほら この世界で今
Look, in this world right now
解き放って
Release it
鋭くギラつかせた希望
A sharp, glittering hope
もっと本気出していいよ
It's okay to get even more serious
Ah... Ah... Ah...
HIT ME UP
Come chase me
Everyday I spent crying 'bout almost-loves turned complicated
On the way, yeah, my heart got torn up, shredded, all but dead and
Now they say I, I'm just a masochist, they're sick of it
Boy, take a hint, you ain't gon' ever get this
Pedal to the metal, shootin' straight to the stars
Got a cravin', like the danger on me
Up another level, temptation you just can't deny
Come get a taste but can't say I won't bite
So hit me up!
gonna... ah
In my eyes, not gonna...
Oh, one, two, three, keep on...
pushing for the high, my lover, I gotta run
but it's fun to see you try
So hit me up!
Off the map, I'm gonna take over, my energy up
Speeding up, watch, ready to lock
So hit me up!
Get the stash, I'm upgrading, you know it's on
So hit me up, so hit me up, ah, I never stop
In enemy territory
On the edge of glory
Boys, just watch how I move
Give me that rush
Gonna regret, lose my mind
Boys, run out of time
So hit me up, I've unlocked, volume up
You got a crush?
Such a cliché, your bad boy charms, throw them all right back in your arms
Wasn't enough, you needed more, now you're begging to let you score
Sure you can take it, yeah, all's alright, there might be reason to say goodbye, goodbye
gotta leave you dry
Always trying to play it cool, 20/20 freezing on me
Just the sign of me and you, yes, you like it like that, like that
Engine humming, that's my cue, catch me if you can, you better
Keep up the chase, boy, you're falling behind
Super fine, I'm ahead now, I'm gonna...
In my eyes, not gonna, oh, one, two, three, keep on...
pushing for the high, my lover, I gotta run
but it's fun to see you try
So hit me up!
Off the map, I'm gonna take over, my energy up
Speeding up, watch, ready to lock
So hit me up!
Get the stash, I'm upgrading, you know it's on
So hit me up, so hit me up, ah, I never stop
In enemy territory
On the edge of glory
Boys, just watch how I move
Give me that rush
Gonna regret, lose my mind
Boys, run out of time
So hit me up, I've unlocked, volume up
You got a crush?
Just barely wasn't enough, you should've...
Ah, you put me on top, you good, girl
Coming full circle, I hit enough
Top spot, dead in hot, watch me run it up
So hit me up!
Rev it up and make that vroom, vroom, vroom, vroom
Hit me up!
When I hit you with that zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom
If you know what's good for you, ooh, ooh
And now I'm back in charge, write that other down
Yeah! I really enjoyed that!
Did you guys enjoy? Did you guys enjoy?
We had a couple of songs with, uh, a couple of important people, which I wanna call in to help with this next MC part.
Special guests! Special guests!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
What's up, みなさん! Hey!
What's up, everyone! Hey!
Introduce yourselves, please!
Please, go ahead.
ホロライブEnglish、CHAD CASTの森カリオペです! What's up, ですです。Hey guys! Hope you enjoyed our performances!
I'm Mori Calliope from HoloLive English, CHAD CAST! What's up, desu desu. Hey guys! Hope you enjoyed our performances!
And... IRyS! It's IRyS, also from CHAD CAST!
Let's go, CHAD!
Ready to rumble!
Yeah!
Wait, what's this movement, walk?
Did you say "rumble"?
I said "rumble".
Oh, oh, right!
I'm pretty sure she just said "IRyS".
Oh, my brain's not working. It's a big day, guys.
Because she's dancing, because she's dancing!
Yeah, it's a big... Guys!
Yeah... Oh yeah, I mean, yeah, obviously, yeah! Woo!
What are you doing? It's so cool! It's so cool! Yeah!
It looks... dynamic. You look like a K-pop star.
Oh, yeah! I'm so glad you like it!
And look, the, the MC tail is back. You know, I gotta put it to rest for a little bit, you know, after all that dancing.
So special. Yeah. Don't touch it. Don't touch it.
But, we, we performed some songs together. Um, first we had Ifuudoudou.
Oh, god. We're going to talk about that? Oh, well, I guess it's on, on brand.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Yeah, we, yeah, we know.
Awesome. Awesome. Great.
It was a sexy song.
How, how do you feel about that song? Thank you so much.
How do I feel? Yeah.
How do you feel about that song?
Feelings, thoughts, opinions...
I feel great about it!
I think it was an amazing...
So hit... hit... So hit me up! Hit me up!
Hit me up! It's so cool. Yeah.
Yeah.
I'm so happy! Well, practice. We practiced so hard.
Yeah, we did! We, every... we practiced so hard.
It's always fun practicing together though. Three of us, two of us at a time. It's always fun.
ねえ、私ダンスしようかな！
Hey, maybe I'll dance!
みんなと私の誕生日にお祝いダンスする！
I'll do a celebration dance on my birthday!
誕生日じゃない、誕生日だけど誕生日じゃない！
Wait, not birthday. Birthday, but not birthday!
誕生日じゃない日に。
On an un-birthday.
非・誕生日。彼女は今「非・誕生」されてるから。
Un-birthday. She's being un-birthed.
でも... その言い方ちょっとヤバくない？
But... that sounds so wrong!
今の発言はポッドキャスト用にとっておきなよ！
Save that for the podcast, IRyS!
でも踊ったら、ちょっとね...
But after dancing, I am feeling a little...
暑い！ 暑くなってきた！脱いじゃう？
Hot! It's getting hot! Is she gonna strip?
うわー！BANされる！ それはマズいよ。
Whoa! That's age-restricted! Maybe not.
すぐ戻るからね！ 何を脱ぐ気なの？
I'll be right back! What is she taking off?
ズボン脱ぐの？ なんでズボンを脱ぐのよ、アイリス！
Is she taking off her pants? Why pants, IRyS?!
一体何を考えてるの？
What are you thinking about?
もう、あなたを止めなきゃ。
Alright, you need to be stopped.
あ、戻ってきた？ おお。
Oh, she's coming back? Oh.
ジャジャーン！ おお、見て！
Behold! Whoa, look at that!
上着脱いじゃった！ 超オシャレじゃん！
I took off my jacket! You look so fancy!
これでもう全部、アクセサリーが見えるでしょ？
Now you can see all my accessories, right?
カッコいい！ トゲトゲもいいね。
Cool! I love the spikes too.
あとアームカフも付けたんだよね。
And I have an arm cuff now as well.
おお、いいね！ カッコいい！
Oh, nice! Cool!
これで何の縛りもなくもっと踊れるよ！
Now I can dance even more with no restrictions!
さらにダイナミックになったね！ 動きやすい？
She's even more dynamic! Is it easier to move?
ツインテールも邪魔にならないしね。
No pigtails to get in the way either.
腕の自由度が上がったね。
More freedom for your arms.
まあせっかくなのでね、こうやって集まったし...
Well, since we're all here together...
もう一曲一緒に歌うのはどうかな？
How would you feel about doing one more song?
いいね！ 体力ないけど頑張る！
Okay! I don't have the energy, but I'll try!
がんばれ、がんばれ！ いけるよ！
Do your best, do your best! You can do it!
というわけで、皆さんも準備はいいですか？
That being said, are you all ready too?
もう一つのパフォーマンスをお届けします！
We're going to bring you another performance!
準備はいい？せーの...
Are you ready? One, two...
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
あじまう あじまう あじまーう！
It's habbening, habbening, habbening!
宿題が全ッッ然終わらない、全国のヤバめな諸君！
To all of ye in big, big trouble, 'cause your homework won't get done
時間がなければ眠らなきゃ良いじゃない
If you're running outta time, you just gotta stay up all night
がんばれ がんばれ あたし！
Hang in there! Don't give up, me!
パーリラ脳内フロア
Get down on the dance floor in your mind
暴れてるカルナバル
We're going wild in this carnival
アドレナリンドバドバ
Pumping the adrenaline
究極のpanight
This is the ultimate PANIGHT
パリナイ！パリナイ！パーラ パッパ パリナイ！
Party night! Party night! Pa-pa-pa-pa, party night!
パリナイ！パリナイ！おわるくナイ？
Party night! Party night! This is good, can't deny
we are NEGI☆U we are NEGI☆U we are NEGI☆U let's go!
スゴい ヤバい パない 物足りない
Oh my, hoo boy, time's tight, it makes me sigh
ないない尽くしで とめとない
Too little, too much in short supply
スゴい ヤバい パない saturday night
Oh my, hoo boy, time's tight, Saturday night
とにかくもう やるしかない どすこい
Nothing to it, go hard and enjoy, now fight!
ヤバい パない 物足りない
Hoo boy, time's tight, it makes me sigh
全力モノモノ申したい
I so want to give you all a piece of my mind
たった一度の青春は
You only get one lifetime
毎日enjoy party night
So enjoy every day and party night
あー お集りの旦那様
Test, test, all the husbands in the house
えー、そうじゃない様、ご唱和ください
And everyone else too, join the chorus
それゆけsay
All together, say
wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow
d-d-d-dj!
パン パン パン パン パン パン パン...
Pam, pam, pam, pam, pam, pam, pam...
うわぁぁ！
Waaaah!
everybody, sing along
でっち上げ進化論
Make it up, the theory's strong
陽キャでも陰キャでも
Extroverts and introverts
勉強だ wassup, wassup!
Time to cram, wassup! Wassup!
太陽は銀河系？
The sun and Milky Way?
おしゃぺり ノンノンノン！
Talking in class is a no-no-no!
遊んじゃダメダメ
Fool around, have hell to pay, pay
ごめんなさーい！
We're sorry, ma'am!
朝が来て 眠れない どうしよう
The sun is up now, but I cannot sleep, what do I do?
神様も両手挙げて fly high
The gods have lost hope letting their hands fly high
なんとかするしかない
But you gotta get it done
頑張れ 出来るって
Grind hard and you can pull it off
ド派手にカマしちゃる
Fine, we'll blow all their minds
ネバギバ put your hands up
Never give up, put your hands up
タリナイ！タリナイ！ターラ タッタ タリナイ！
Things ain't fine! Things ain't fine! Th-th-th-this ain't fine!
タリナイ！タリナイ！時間がない
Things ain't fine! Things ain't fine! We're running out of time!
we are NEGI☆U we are NEGI☆U we are NEGI☆U let's go!
（あ、えっと、れっつごー）
(Oh, uh... let's go...?)
スゴい ヤバい パない 物足りない
Oh my, hoo boy, time's tight, it makes me sigh
代打のバッターか たじけない
Thank you so much, pinch hitter of mine
スゴい ヤバい パない sunday night
Oh my, hoo boy, time's tight, Sunday night
とにかくもう やるしかない どすこい
Nothing to it, gotta make the deadline, now fight!
ヤバい パない 物足りない
Hoo boy, time's tight, it makes it sigh
宿題 やっぱり 終わらない
All this homework, no end in sight
たった一度の青春は
You only get one lifetime
脳内 happy party night
Make your mind happy on this party night
ねねちー、あてぃしー
Nenechi, Aqua,
おわんねーよこれー！
there's no end to this!
スバル先輩ー！
Subaru-senpai!
この問題 全然わかんないんですけど！
I don't know the answer to this at all!
えーっ！何その鉛筆！
Wait, what's with your pencil?
めっちゃ可愛いじゃん、いいなー！
That's so cute, lucky you!
でしょー！
I know, right?
キラキラ光るんですよー ホホホ
It glows and all that, ohoho!
え、へへ、みんな、げんきだなぁ
Uh, haha... you guys are so full of life.
よ、陽キャって、こんな時も すごいなー
N-normies will be normies, huh? Wow...
ぱ、ぱーりー！
P-party...?
お書きになったそんな音楽は
The music you have written...
現在使われておりません。もう一度お書き直しください。
...is not currently in use. Please rewrite it once more.
意味わかんねぇ！
I don't get it!
どーせ誰も聴いてなんかいないさ
No one is listening anyway,
音楽なんて全部ファッション
music is all just fashion.
音亡喰らって選手退場ワンナイト
Washed out by the sound, player exit, one night.
どーせ何も伝えてなんかいないさ
Nothing is being conveyed anyway.
なんとかトック撮って売名
Shooting some Tik Tok to clout-chase,
あんな気取っておいて最低グンナイ
so pretentious, it's the worst, good night.
どうしたってどうみたって
No matter what, no matter how you look at it,
尊師たちでもう大渋滞
it's already crowded with gurus.
それでもあっち、こっち、そっち、ぼっち、
Even so, here, there, over there, all alone,
卍, zエイジ猿も欲しがる
Manji, Gen Z monkeys all want it.
パンチライン欲しいの？
Do you want a punchline?
意味とかどっちだっていいよ
I don't care either way about the meaning.
歌詞とかどうでもいいので
I don't care about the lyrics,
ノれるのください
so just give me something to groove to!
さぁ皆で笑いましょう
Come on, let's all laugh together.
芸術より数の大小？
Is quantity more important than art?
ヴァイラスに酷い代償
A terrible price paid to the virus.
じゃあどうすんの？それでいいんだっけ？
So what are we gonna do? Is that really okay?
頭は空回り死んでいく
My mind spins out of control and dies.
I found myself instead
ふざけるな!!!
Don't screw with me!
バイバイバズメロディー
Bye-bye, buzzing melody.
疑えよ大概嘘ばかり
Doubt it, for it's mostly lies.
化けんな 幻想でも理想でも良い
Don't fake it, whether it's an illusion or an ideal.
君の歌いたかった物はどうしたんだい？
What happened to the thing you wanted to sing?
ぶざまでもオーライ嘘じゃない
Even if it's uncool, it's alright, it's not a lie.
お金や擬奏で満たす前に
Before filling yourself with money or fake play,
負けんな覚醒せよ鼓動達よ
don't lose, awaken, you beating hearts!
君の伝えたかった物はどうしたんだい？
What happened to the thing you wanted to convey?
意味わかんねぇ
I don't get it!
お書きになったそんな音楽は現在使われておりません。
The music you have written is no longer in use.
ポップソング、ヒットソング聴いてもう一度お書き直してください
Listen to pop songs and hit songs, and try rewriting it.
あーもうハイカラ作家ばっか洒落臭いわ はぁ…
Ah, all these stylish writers are so annoying, sigh...
どいつもこいつもそいつもあいつも
Every single one of them, this one, that one, him too,
意味わかんねぇ!!!
I don't get it!!!
どうしたってどうみたって
No matter what, no matter how you look at it,
尊師たちでもう大渋滞
it's already crowded with gurus.
それでもあっち、こっち、そっち、ぼっち、
Even so, here, there, over there, all alone,
卍, zエイジ猿も欲しがる
Manji, Gen Z monkeys all want it.
パンチライン欲しいの？
Do you want a punchline?
意味とかどっちだっていいよ
I don't care either way about the meaning.
歌詞とかどうでもいいので
I don't care about the lyrics,
伸びるのください
so just give me something that will grow!
さぁ皆で祓いましょう
Come on, let's all exorcise it together.
芸術より数なんでしょう？
It's about the numbers rather than the art, right?
ヴァイラスに酷い代償
A terrible price paid to the virus.
じゃあどうすんの？それでいいんだっけ？
So what are we gonna do? Is that really okay?
頭は空回り死んでいく
My mind spins out of control and dies.
I found myself instead
ふざけるな!!!
Don't screw with me!
バイバイバズメロディー
Bye-bye, buzzing melody.
疑えよ大概嘘ばかり
Doubt it, for it's mostly lies.
化けんな 幻想でも理想でも良い
Don't fake it, whether it's an illusion or an ideal.
君の歌いたかった物はどうしたんだい？
What happened to the thing you wanted to sing?
このままじゃ到底終われない
I can't possibly end it like this.
欲しいのはきっとお金じゃない
What I want surely isn't money.
負けんな覚醒せよ鼓動達よ
Don't lose, awaken, you beating hearts!
君の歌いたかった物がきっとあるんだ決まってない
I sure there's something you wanted to sing.
ふざけるな…
Don't screw with me...
ふざけるな!!!
Don't screw with me!
バイバイバズメロディー
Bye-bye, buzzing melody.
疑えよ大概嘘ばかり
Doubt it, for it's mostly lies.
化けんな 幻想でも理想でも良い
Don't fake it, whether it's an illusion or an ideal.
君の歌いたかった物はどうしたんだい？
What happened to the thing you wanted to sing?
ぶざまでもオーライ嘘じゃない
Even if it's uncool, it's alright, it's not a lie.
お金や擬奏で満たす前に
Before filling yourself with money or fake play,
負けんな覚醒せよ鼓動達よ
don't lose, awaken, you beating hearts!
君の歌いたかった物はどうしたんだい？
What happened to the thing you wanted to sing?
意味わかんねぇ!!!
I don't get it!!!
意味わかんねぇよ!!!
意味わかんねぇ!!!
I don't get it!!!
Watch your blood, blood, blood, blood, blood
I'm a V, watch your blood, blood, blood, blood, blood
I'm a V, got a V, got a V, got a V, got a lot of blood, blood, blood, blood, blood
타다가 남은 말라버린 건
What is left of the burnt and dried up...
샤워 한번 하고 나면 씻겨 내려갈 뿐인걸
will just be washed away after taking a shower.
더욱더 미워하고 미워하고 미워하고 미워해 봐
Try hating me more and more and more.
날 어디서 본 것 같다고?
Did you say you saw me somewhere?
愛想笑いでも 免疫があるなら免除
Even with a fake smile, if you have immunity, you're exempt.
とか腹立たせてる 言ってるメンタルは？ あーあー
Getting angry and saying things like that, what is your mental state? Ah, ah...
最高スマイルで 壊してファントム
Destroy the phantom with your best smile.
ごまかしたり慎重に サバイバルならバイバイ
Faking it or playing it safe? If it's survival, then bye-bye.
ねぇ、死んだ？
Hey, are you dead?
I'm a V, I'm a V, I'm a wild, wild, yo
I'm a V, got a V, got a lot of wild, wild
夢見てる少女ね 夢見てる少女ね
You're a dreaming girl, a dreaming girl.
V なら V だわ 甘甘甘甘の
If it's V, then it's V, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet.
정리 칼같이 벌써
It's already cleaned up as sharp as a knife.
소리쳐봐 센터, 우리가 센터
Scream center, we are the center!
달려라 관객석의 판다
Run, panda in the audience!
우리는 난다, 머리가 운다 주고받은 소통
We fly, our head cries, interaction given and received.
M-I-V, M-I-C, alive, alive, M-I-C, so light, so light, why, why, miss you...
Now let me...
惚れました？エモいモンスター
Did you fall in love, you emotional monster?
My name is VDOL 乱れたら最期 儚くもラヴドール
My name is VDOL; if you lose control, it's the end, a fleeting love doll
I'm a VDOL, not about talk
心の中 smooth like a butter
Smooth like butter inside your heart
Touch me したいなら ほらエンドレス
If you want to touch me, look, it's endless
Catch me したいハイピース
With a high peace sign, catch me
魅惑するスワッグわからない
I don't understand this enchanting swag
暴れる心叫ぶ ひとつ の ライフ
A wild heart screaming out a single life
生きる姿や魂を今
My living form and soul now...
２つにして愛をバラバラに
...split them in two, tearing love to pieces
生まれた時の喜びは暴走に
The joy from when I was born turns into a rampage
さようならでいいの？
Is it okay to say goodbye?
だめね
No way
わっちゃわっちゃ
Watcha watcha
わっちゃわっちゃ Make-up! Make-up!
Watcha watcha, make up, make up
わっちゃわっちゃ
Watcha watcha
わっちゃわっちゃ Make-up! Make-up! la
Watcha watcha, make up, make up, la
楽観のロカネ あららっ好感で紹介ね sounding like a rockabilly
The rockabilly of optimism, oh, introduced with good favor
撤退招待ね あら
An invitation to retreat, oh
わっちゃわっちゃ Make-up! Make-up!
Watcha watcha, make up, make up
楽観のロカネ あららっ好感で紹介ね
The rockabilly of optimism, oh, introduced with good favor
いっかんの終わりね あんなんてない
That's the end of the line, nothing like that
I am a V, I am a V, I am a ワーワーワーよ
I am a V, I am a V, I am a wah wah wah
I am a V-doll, I'm a diva, 乱れワーワーワーよ
I am a V-doll, I'm a diva, going wild, wah wah wah
夢見てる少年が 夢見てる少女で
The dreaming boy is a dreaming girl
VならVだわ ワーワーワーワーよ
If it's a V, it's a V, wah wah wah wah
強要さ 子どもの頃言われたもんだ
It's forced, I was told ever since I was a kid
あのヒーローショーの人形の背中には
On the back of the doll from that hero show...
チャックはついてないからな 泣くな
...there is no zipper, so don't cry
末路はダイヒューマンだ 死ぬのこの優雅
The end is a die-human, dying this elegantly
存在はワンワンだ
Existence is just a woof-woof
吠えても惚れても 死ぬまでバラバラだ
Whether barking or falling in love, we're in pieces until death
わっちゃわっちゃ わっちゃわっちゃ
Watcha watcha, watcha watcha
わわわわっ！
Wa-wa-wa-wah!
わっちゃわっちゃ わっちゃわっちゃ
Watcha watcha, watcha watcha
Are you ready for...?
惚れたら死ぬぞ
If you fall in love, you'll die
わっちゃわっちゃ わっちゃわっちゃ
Watcha watcha, watcha watcha
I'm a V
Oh! Okay...
疲れた！ I'm so tired!
I'm exhausted! I'm so tired!
I hope you guys have been enjoying the show!
We had so many bangers after bangers after bangers!
A lot of dancing, we had PONLIGHT, we had Cyberpunk Dead Boy, we had V...
My arms are dead, everything dead.
But, that's not the end of the show yet! We gotta keep going on and on and on and on!
And here, I bring you a very, very, very important and...
...exciting announcement!
I am about to perform a song that no one has heard before.
No one! Except for me, because...
...IT'S MY NEW SONG!!!
I've been hyping this up for a while now, because I'm really, really excited...
...and this will be the first time that I'm sharing it with all of you, so I hope you enjoy.
More info after I perform it, because you gotta see it first, you know?
Wish me luck! I'm nervous, but we got this!
これからは、私の新曲です！
From here on, it's my new song!
あの、めちゃくちゃ緊張なんだけど、頑張って...
Um, I'm super nervous, but I'll do my best...
...パフォーマンスしたいと思います！ どうぞ！
...and perform it! Please enjoy!
준비!
Get ready!
That’s good game, what a shame
Players they all complain
Why me? No, not again
Shout ra-ta-ta, but...
Ain’t got time, so dry those eyes
Look around, what’s that I spy?
The broken and bruised
I’ve got something to prove now
Abracadabra, let's go
Watch them like dust as they fall
끝까지 가보자 go
Let's go until the end, go
나는 내 맘대로 해
I do whatever I want
Double one, double win
Lowly to lottery
Do or die
We hit that high (snake eyes, snake eyes)
We hit that high / Snake eyes, snake eyes
Come on, don’t be shy (snake eyes, snake eyes)
Come on, don’t be shy / Snake eyes, snake eyes
뜨겁게 따라 올라
Chasing and rising hotly
놀자 all day, all night
Let's play all day, all night
So turn it up, can't stop, won't stop preachin'
Who said the sky’s a limit
Show them that we mean business
We are the young and vicious
Snake eyes, they never lie
Fly high with pride and leave your fears behind
지겨워
I'm sick of it
우리들의 광란의 party
Our frantic party
보여줄게 환상 safari
I'll show you a fantasy safari
Baddie, baddie, nobody can stop me
끼리끼리 붙어, come on closer
Stick together, come on closer
Go, go, 더 빨리
Go, go, faster
Actin' all naughty
싹 다 부셔 모조리
Smash it all completely
모조리 싹다 다다다
Completely, all of it, da-da-da
Shake it off, what goes around
Shut your mouth, will come back down
Ready the fight
Ready the screaming
Abracadabra, let's go
Watch it, we reapin' it all
꺾이지 않는 의지
An unbending will
될 대로 돼 볼래 play
I'll play, let it be
Reason, our demon
Believe in the beaten
Just wait and see
We hit that high
Snake eyes, snake eyes
Come on, don't be shy
뜨겁게 따라 올라
Rising hotly
불타올라
Burning up
놀자 all day
Let's play all day
all night
all day, all night
Let the beat drop
Go!
We go hard
기사회생 전부를 걸어 bet
Survival, risking everything, bet
Go, we go hard
We want it all
다시 일어나 파괴와 재생
Rise up again, destruction and rebirth
죽지 않아, 전부 걸어
I won't die, bet everything
맞서 싸워, 시작이야
Fight back, it's the beginning
Take the crown
끝까지 달려가 rule
Run to the end, rule
We’ll hit that high
Snake eyes, snake eyes
Come on, don't be shy
같이 춤을 춰 봐
Let's dance together
이렇게
like this
멈출 순 없어
Can't stop
같이 dance all night
dance all night together
Don't be afraid of losing
It's just a new beginning
Look at the cards we dealing
Sometimes it takes a villain
Snake eyes, the time is nigh
Fly high with pride
And leave your fears behind
It's finally out!
I hope you all enjoyed my new song, Snake Eyes!
Snake Eyes! Snake Eyes! Snake Eyes! Snake Eyes! Snake Eyes!
This has been such a long process in...
...in the making! I can't even talk!
I'm exhausted, but also I'm so happy! It's finally out!
My newest song, Snake Eyes, was what I just performed.
Not only is it...
...the first time that, you know, I've written a lot of the lyrics from scratch,
you know, but also...
...it's my first time choreographing...
...you know, a multi-member song, multi-member with, you know, the two back dancers!
I'm so happy!
I did it! I hope you guys enjoyed it.
Now, very important, pay attention!
The MV of the new song is also going to be premiering very soon after the live is over.
And it is going to be...
...my first ever 3D music video!
I'm so excited! やっとね、新曲が
I'm so excited! Finally, my new song...
ちょっとね、あの、公開するんで、めちゃくちゃ
...is going to be released, so I'm incredibly...
嬉しいです。えーと、このあとライブの後ね
...happy. Also, after this live...
あの、初の3D MVもプレミア公開するので
...my first 3D MV will premiere, so...
あの、見てください！お願いします！
...please watch it! I beg of you!
歌詞、え、英語の歌詞は、ほぼ、あの、自分で書いたので
The lyrics, well, the English lyrics were almost entirely written by myself, so...
あと韓国語もね、あの、頑張ってたんで、あの
and I also worked hard on the Korean, so...
聴いてください！
...please listen to it!
Streaming should also begin shortly after as well.
It should be, um, local time midnight, I never know anything, but...
...it'll happen soon.
So please make sure to check it out afterwards!
Oh, I hope I did okay.
I don't know, I was stressed about the choreography for a very long time, but...
...now...
...it's time. It's the thing you've all been waiting for.
A merch showcase!
グッズ紹介に入りたいと思います！
I'd like to move on to the merch showcase!
This is the lineup for this time! Ta-da!
...always look at it, yes!
And it's just really pretty. Look at it.
Look at it, it's so pretty.
Thank you so much!
あの、ママ、今年もね、Mikaママに、あの、イラスト描いてくださったので、あざます。
Um, Mama, this year too, Mika Mama drew an illustration for me, so thank you.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
ぜひぜひ、買ってください。
Please buy it by all means!
And, what's the next item? Second is...
Tadah! The ReCOLOR Plushie Keychain...
...designed after my new outfit!
I've always wanted like a mini, you know, plushie that I came out with.
Um, you know, I have some, but I think it was just really fitting because I have a new outfit...
...and I wanted a plushie in the new outfit. I can take her around places, you know?
And, you know, you can photograph her, chuck her, I don't know, take a... pat her, I don't know, whatever you want to do.
But it's a plushie keychain, so it comes with a ball chain, so you can attach it to your bag!
Look! Isn't she so cute?
Look at those squishy cheeks! めっちゃ可愛いでしょ？
Look at those squishy cheeks! It's so cute, right?
あの、ぬいぐるみキーホルダーなんで、なんかカバンにつけたりとかね、できるので...
Um, since it's a plushie keychain, you can do things like attach it to your bag...
めちゃくちゃ可愛い感じになりました。あざます。
...it turned out to be super cute. Thank you.
えーっと、次！What's the next one?
Um, next! What's the next one?
これです！
This is it!
The Lil Plushie Shed Pouch!
It is a pouch. It is a pouch for...
...the plushie. If you get both, it's like a set, you know? Because, you know, you want to take your little Bae out...
...into the world, but what if she gets dirty, you know?
Or like, you know, you don't want her to get... if she gets snagged on a corner and she rips?
You gotta protect your little Bae, so you have a Lil Plushie Shed...
...to house your little Bae!
But it fits perfectly, and you know, you can use it. The design is also really cool as well.
Next! Last but not least...
...is something very special. It is a voice pack.
But, it is my first ever ASMR voice pack!
Um, I get really embarrassed doing ASMR stuff, but I just thought...
...you know, since it's a special occasion, maybe it'd be nice to have my very first ASMR voice pack.
It features an intimate scene with you guys after the live show.
So if you want to, you know, check it out, please do.
僕、初、初のASMRボイス、シナリオボイスなんで...
This is my very first ASMR voice, a scenario voice, so...
もし、気になってる方はぜひ聞いてください。
...if you're interested, please be sure to listen to it.
ありがとうございます。It's called 'Forever Your Bae'. 恥ずかしい。
Thank you so much. It's called 'Forever Your Bae'. It's embarrassing.
Anyway! Here are the full set purchases!
The postcard! You get a limited edition, which...
...the limited edition, sorry, features a hand-signed autograph...
...and also a handwritten message from yours truly, just a extra way to say thank you very much.
And standard version comes with the foil-stamped duplicate autograph and message.
I'm about to, about to die, but it's alright! Thank you so much.
えっと、とく、とく、とく、やばい、読め！
Um, bo- bo- bo- oh no, read it!
漢字がなんだっけ？とく、特典はこちらです！
What was the kanji again? Th- The bonus is this!
あざます。ポストカード、えっと...
Thank you. The postcard, um...
あの、ひ、ひ、き、ひ、き、ひ、き、ひ、き、直筆サイン！
Um, h- h- h- hand-signed autograph!
とメッセージがあります。ありがとうございます。
And a message is included. Thank you very much.
Oh my god, my brain is just... it's gone. I'm so tired. But anyway, um, I think that's it.
Oh wait, no! There's also a bonus voice! Wait, I forgot.
Um, so with the full set, there is a bonus voice pack that is also ASMR, that's on top of the already ASMR voice pack.
Just a little extra thing to say thank you.
That's it. I'm embarrassed. Anyway, yes.
それだけです！あざます！はい！
That's it! Thank you! Yes!
Before we continue, I guess there is a little bit after, so I'm gonna go put my jacket on real quick...
...if that's okay. I'll be right back.
ちょっと着替えてきます。
I'll go change real quick.
Tadah! 戻ってきました。はい。
Tadah! I'm back. Yes.
ただいまです。えっと、just put on my jacket.
I'm back. Um, just put on my jacket.
I'm so happy that, you know, I got to do another birthday live this year, even though it's not really my birthday.
Um, I'm so happy that I got to show my new outfit.
I'm just happy that I got a new outfit.
It's so easy to dance in, I love the way it looks.
And today, I got to dance with so many of my friends!
It was so much fun.
I got to challenge myself. It's always an amazing, amazing experience being able to do a birthday live.
いや、今日ね、あの...
No, today, um...
...いっぱいメンバーと一緒に踊ってめちゃくちゃ嬉しくて...
...dancing with so many of the members made me super happy...
...新衣装もめちゃくちゃ嬉しくて、とにかく嬉しいです。
...and the new outfit made me super happy too. I'm just so happy!
あの、みんなもね、
Um, everyone too,
There's a lot of planning that goes into these, lots of staff and everyone.
スタッフさんもね、みんなもね...
The staff too, everyone too...
Everyone's 力...
Everyone's power...
...が必要。もう、なんだこれ。
...is needed. Man, what is this?
もう英語か日本語かも分かんないっす。すいません、はい。
I don't even know if I'm speaking English or Japanese. Sorry!
I'm just mixing up my languages, but...
Please do check out the new song MV that's coming out shortly.
I'm really, really proud of it.
Um, but that's kind of it. That's all I have for today.
But there is a final encore song that I wanted to sing...
...that I think really sums up today's live.
So, if you would like to stay till... Please stay to the end!
Please listen, please don't go anywhere.
ちょっとこの後、最後の一曲あります。
After this, we have one last song.
今日のテーマにぴったりの曲だと思いますので、最後まで聴いてください。
I think it's a song perfect for today's theme, so please listen to the end.
はい！
Yes!
あと新曲のMVも見てくださいね。はい、はい。
Also, please make sure to watch the new MV, too! Okay?
あ、じゃあ、最後の曲、ラスト曲、どうぞ！
Well then, here is the last song, the final song! Please listen!
魂の色は 何色ですか
What is the color of the soul?
Thank you for coming to my live today!
I hope I brought some color to your day!
最後まで盛り上がっていこうぜ！
Let's keep the energy up until the very end!
「もういっそ 折れたままで」
"I'd rather it stay broken"
捨てるほど 逃げ出すほど
I'm not strong enough to discard it
強くないよ ほら自ずと
or run away, look...
もう一度 鼓動高鳴る
The heartbeat quickens once more
何が正しいかなんて
Though I don't know
わからないけど
what is right...
形のないものばかりが 大切になって行く
Only things without form become precious
飾らない言葉だけが 強く結ばれてる
Only unadorned words are tied strongly
また躓いて 転がって それでも砕けない
I stumble and tumble again, yet I don't break
魂の色は 何色ですか
What is the color of the soul?
ただ傷ついて 強がって それでも見つけたいよ
Just hurt, acting tough, yet I still want to find it
魂のカタチ 確かめてるよ
I am confirming the shape of the soul
深い地の底で一人
Alone at the bottom of the deep earth
扉と鍵を探す
I search for the door and the key
おとぎ話は ほら
The fairy tale, look...
泡の様に全部消えて
disappears completely like bubbles
葛藤 残像だけ
Only conflict and afterimages remain
次の頁へ
toward the next page
伸びてく枝葉が分かれて それぞれの道を行く
Extending branches divide, each going their own way
寂しい思い出だけが 強く根を張ってる
Only lonely memories strike deep roots
また貫いて失って それでも挫けない
I pierce through and lose again, yet I do not falter
心はどこに 器はどこに
Where is the heart? Where is the vessel?
ただ残されて抜け落ちて
Just left behind, slipped away
それでも伝えたいよ
yet I still want to convey it
魂の日々を
The days of the soul...
魂の意志を
The will of the soul...
ずっと ずっと
Forever, forever
魂の色は
What is the color of the soul?
何色ですか
What color is it?
赤い色ですか
Is it red?
青い色ですか
Is it blue?
魂の色は 魂の色は
What is the color of the soul? What is the color of the soul?
何色ですか 何色ですか
What color is it? What color is it?
透明な過去に 不透明な明日に
In the transparent past and the opaque tomorrow
生きるあなたは 何色ですか
What color are you living as?
また躓いて 転がって それでも砕けない
I stumble and tumble again, yet I don't break
魂の色は 何色ですか
What is the color of the soul?
ただ傷ついて 強がって それでも見つけたいよ
Just hurt, acting tough, yet I still want to find it
魂のカタチ 確かめてるよ
I am confirming the shape of the soul
確かめてるよ
...I'm checking it
ずっと
Forever...
Woah Woah Woah
ずっと
Forever...
Woah Woah Woah
ずっと
Forever...
Woah Woah Woah
ずっと
Forever...
Woah Woah Woah
2026.2.28 NEW 3D OUTFIT?! ReCOLOUR Hakos Baelz Birthday Live 2026